{
    "subject": "resource/William_Zeckendorf",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1905-06-30",
    "human_readable": "William Zeckendorf was born on 30th June 1905.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8941044807434082,
            "question": "When was William Zeckendorf born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7826794981956482,
            "question": "Where was William Zeckendorf born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.75925612449646,
            "question": "What month was William Zeckendorf born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.622757613658905,
            "question": "What is William Zeckendorf known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5688299536705017,
            "question": "Is there any information available about William Zeckendorf's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5510187745094299,
            "question": "Was William Zeckendorf a mathematician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5317652225494385,
            "question": "What was William Zeckendorf's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4871757924556732,
            "question": "In what year did William Zeckendorf come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3297654092311859,
            "question": "Did William Zeckendorf make any significant contributions to science?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2947786748409271,
            "question": "What are some of the most important facts about William Zeckendorf's life and work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=William Zeckendorf was born on 30th June 1905.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8812_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did William Zeckendorf make any significant contributions to science?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8812_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did William Zeckendorf come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8812_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was William Zeckendorf's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8812_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8812_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8812_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8812_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8812_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8812_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8812_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8812_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8812_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8812_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8812_42.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states that William Zeckendorf was born in 1842, not 1905. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nReasoning:\nThe document provides information about William Zeckendorf's birth year as 1842, not his date of birth or the specific day (June 30) in which he was born. The triple \"William Zeckendorf was born on 30th June 1905\" cannot be confirmed by the provided context."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not support the statement that William Zeckendorf was born on June 30, 1905. According to the documents, William Zeckendorf was born in 1842, which contradicts the given date of birth."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "William Zeckendorf was born in 1842, not in 1905.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "He was born in 1842.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "William Zeckendorf was born in 1842, as stated in the context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "William Zeckendorf was born in 1842, not 1905.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}